♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
And so my mom says,
“I’m not gonna let you
go out dressed like that!”
And then she says,
“Just look at your T-shirt.
You see your navel!”
Well, you know me,
I tell her, “Listen, mom,
everyone dresses like that.
It’s the latest style!”
So then she says…
Hold it a second.
It’s Ulrich.
Just look at him!
Oh, how can anybody
be that handsome!
Hello, little ones.
Aren’t we a bit
wet behind the ears
to be looking at boys?
I don’t believe it.
Look at yourselves!
You’ve even got
a drop of milk
from your bottle
on your cheek!
(CHUCKLES)
She believed you, Sissi!
Not only is she a baby,
but she’s also dumb.
Hey, Nicholas, you should
defender her, not insult her.
You dumbells
ought to stick together.
Besides, girls, you’re setting
your sights much too high.
Ulrich’s way
out of your league.
Why don’t you just
go back to your dolls
and stop dreaming?
Oh, yeah?
You think that just because
you’re a few years older
and play the snob that
all you have to do
is snap your fingers
and he’ll come running, huh?
I don’t think--I know.
There isn’t a boy in school
who isn’t dying to go out with me.
Stick around and learn.
Hi, how are you?
Well, what do you know?
It’s Miss Conceded in person.
Nobody asked you, creep!
So, Ulrich, when are you
going to stop being so shy
and finally tell me
how you feel about me, huh?
You’re wrong, I’m not shy.
Not at all.
I’m just allergic to
anyone who’s stuck up.
And in that category,
you win hands down.
(LAUGHTER)
I’ll bet she’s
been telling you
how nobody
can resist her charm.
She’s right, too.
Just take a look
at the two nobodies
she’s always
hanging out with.
Take it easy.
Wow.
You ought to be a dog trainer
when you grow up.
Go on. Laugh all you want.
Show your friends
how clever you are,
but I see the way you look at me
when they’re not around!
I think she’s hallucinating.
Oh, no. Speaking of dogs,
I have to go and feed Kiwi.
I'll go with you.
Wanna come? Huh, Yumi?
I’ll see you later.
I promised Jeremie
I’d stop by and see him.
Jeremie?
Hi, Yumi, come in.
What are you doing?
I’m working on a new program.
A sort of catastrophe
alarm system.
The idea is to rate
non-natural disasters
on a scale of one to ten.
And once I’ve got it finished,
I’m gonna get it
onto every website,
or information network
if you like,
and any time the system
registers a disaster
that rates higher than five,
it automatically informs me.
And then what?
It’s the surest way
for me to identify
a possible XANA attack.
Wow. That’s cool.
What’s on your mind?
Well, it…it’s Ulrich.
I wonder…do you think
he likes Sissi?
Sissi? You’re kidding.
Come on!
You know, I never
would’ve believed it,
but you’re really jealous,
aren’t you?
What? You’re kidding!
How could you think
for a minute
that I could be
jealous of that dimwit!
That is ridiculous!
Hey, eat a little slower,
Kiwi, will you?
You look like Nicholas
in the lunchroom!
Don’t insult my dog, huh!
His manners
are ten times better
than that sloppy airhead!
I got a great idea
that might be fun.
What do you say we
take our friend Sissi
down a peg or two?
There’s nothing in the world
I would rather do.
What’s your idea, huh?
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
A message!
“You’re the fairest of them all.
I can’t resist you.
Meet me in the garden shed.”
Ah, I knew it!
(PULSING)
Do you read me?
I repeat, do you read me?
What’s going on?
I can’t contact any aircraft.
Hey, they traffic lights
are all blocked.
The city’s gonna be
in total gridlock!
The subway trains
aren’t stopping anywhere.
What’s going on?
I don’t know, but I’ve got
a sort of eye on the monitor.
The trains switches
aren’t responding.
The trains are out of control!
Have you contacted
the conductors?
Most of them.
The problem is that
trains 3611 and 9432
are completely automatic.
And they’re on a collision course
and I can’t stop them!
They’re freight trains--
no passengers.
How long before they collide?
26 minutes.
But the 3611 is
a special convoy train
carrying a load of
highly toxic chemicals.
One last adjustment,
and the program should
be ready.
There we go.
Now there’s nothing left to do
but wait until
XANA rears his evil head.
A mysterious
and powerful virus
infected all of the country’s
main computer systems
just a few minutes ago.
The infrastructures affected
are very numerous and vital.
They include communication,
banking, all subway systems,
and air traffic control.
The most imminent danger,
however, is the probability
of a major train crash.
For more information,
here’s John Swamp.
Thank you, Ellen.
That’s right. Two freight trains
are on a collision course.
and one of the trains
is carrying highly toxic chemicals,
which if spread
into the atmosphere,
would cause an unprecedented
environmental catastrophe.
John, is there any way
of preventing this disaster?
None at all
for the simple reason
that the trains are
both computer-operated
and therefore impossible
to control at this time.
It’ll take a miracle to stop them.
The authorities are
considering an evacuation
of the local population.
You try to warn
Ulrich and Odd.
I’ll head over to the lab
to contact Aelita
and prepare the transfers.
Uh-oh.
Yumi’s trying to reach us.
She’s gonna blow our cover.
Got you.
I’ll shut off my cell phone.
What’s going on with them?
Come on, one of you
has got to be able to answer.
I’m here, Ulrich!
Oh, what is
going on around here!
(BOTH LAUGH)
Irresistible Sissi.
You’re right.
Not even a dog
can resist your charms.
Hey, don’t knock it, Ulrich.
This is a step up, huh?
because Herb and Nicholas
are no match for Kiwi!
Sorry to drag you away, Kiwi.
You’ll pay for this!
That’s okay.
As soon as you’re all dry,
send us the bill. Ciao!
Kiwi, go home now.
Go on. Go home, boy.
That’s it.
It’s a shame
we didn’t take a picture.
Yeah, imagine the headline
in Milly and Tamiya’s newspaper!
Sissi and Kiwi--
An Impossible Romance!
(GRUNTS)
I seem to recall
a school rule that says
pets are strictly
forbidden on campus.
Rules are made
to be obeyed.
Aelita, do you read me?
Yes.
I was working on your
latest materialization program.
Forget it for now.
There’s no time.
We’ve got a big problem.
XANA’s launched an attack.
Have you noticed anything?
No, but I’ll go
have a look around.
Yumi, were you
able to contact them?
No, they’ve
shut their mobiles off.
I’m out looking for them.
Where in the world
can they be?
(YELPS)
That’s it.
Go beddy bye now,
you horrible little mongrel.
Oh, Yumi,
you got here too late.
You missed a great show.
Sissi’s got herself a boyfriend.
Although, boy’s
not exactly the right word.
Anyway, they’re in love.
Hey, I’ve been trying
to reach you for 15 minutes!
Thanks, guys.
XANA has just
launched an attack.
Okay, I read you. It’s urgent.
Hey, you there!
Oh, no no no!
As if we didn’t have
enough problems!
So, it seems you
forgot the rules
here at school, huh?
Pets are not allowed!
Yeah, we know
that, Jim, but…
you’re not gonna
make a big deal
out of a little dog, are you?
That’s for the principal to decide.
Follow me.
You’re even a worse
pain in the neck than I thought.
How could she do such a thing.
She got her revenge,
but we can’t worry about it now.
There’s no time.
Come on, there are
too many lives at stake.
The situation remains unchanged.
The two freight trains
are completely out of control.
Army units have begun
to evacuate the people
in the immediate area.
Now for other news
around the country.
The capital is in
a state of total gridlock.
Huge traffic jams
are creating chaos
and the police are
totally swamped
and unable to help.
And since all
alarm systems are down,
there’s a tremendous
amount of looting.
Got anything new, Aelita?
Yes, I do, Jeremie.
I’ve picked up pulsations
and it seems that
the activated tower
is in the desert.
I’m on my way.
Hey, where’s Odd?
He’s in the principal’s office
because Jim
found out about Kiwi.
Okay, you two.
Get ready for immediate departure.
Do we really have to stay here?
Don’t be like that! Come on, Jim!
You heard the principal.
You’ve got to stay
in the study hall
until your parents get here
and pick up that mutt!
And I’m gonna stay here
and keep an eye on you!
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Yumi.
Scanner Ulrich.
Scanner Yumi.
Virtualization.
Everything’s cool, Jeremie.
The transfer was successful.
No problem.
And Aelita’s here.
Okay, great.
And no monsters in sight.
Any news from Odd?
No, not yet.
I’ll try to contact him.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Huh?
Well, what do you know.
Huh? What’d you say?
Uh…nothing, nothing.
I uh…I have to go
outside for a minute.
Dogs have, well,
they have certain needs.
If you know what I mean.
Forget it.
What he needs
is to get some sleep.
The tower is there.
That’s too easy.
Yeah, looks like
a real XANA trap.
Hey, Jeremie,
do you see anything
on your screen?
No, nothing.
Not even a single monster.
Hey, Kiwi, come on.
Wake up.
Want a biscuit? Huh?
A nice big doggy biscuit?
Huh?
(BARKS)
Hey, what’s the matter with him?
I warned you if I don’t
take him out for a walk,
you’re gonna have
some mopping up to do!
You think I’m stupid, huh?
As soon as you’re outside,
you’ll take off, right?
Me? I wouldn’t do that, Jim!
Okay, now. Stop.
You can’t pull that one on me.
I’m gonna take
the dog out myself,
and you’re gonna stay put
and not move, you got that?
Fourteen minutes.
Just fourteen minutes left
before the two trains
collide with each other.
Alert!
You’re surrounded by
four monsters!
Where are they?
I don’t see any monsters.
Yumi, Ulrich,
get out of there now!
You’re losing
too many life points!
Great idea.
Only how
do you suggest we do it?
Sprout wings, huh!
There are a lot of rocks
on your right.
Try and lose them in there.
Yumi, take Aelita
away with you.
I’ll handle them.
But Ulrich!
Don’t argue! Run!
Triplicate!
Go!
Impact!
Well? Are you gonna
do it or not?
How you doing, Jim?
Walking your wittle doggie?
(BOTH GIGGLE)
Okay, you had your chance.
We’re going back now.
Hm?
I don’t believe it.
Oh, no!
Yeah!
Hey, did I miss the party?
I guess you could say that.
Ulrich has the grand total
of 10 life points left.
What about the trains?
8 minutes to impact.
Better get a move on.
Impact!
Run!
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization.
Telekinesis.
The coast is clear!
Aah!
Oh, no!
Jeremie, help!
Hang on.
Odd is on the way.
Welcome back
to our world, Yumi.
I’m sorry.
I did what I could.
Aelita, you’re crazy!
What are you doing!
Get out of there now!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Yes!
I was sure she would do that.
Laser arrow!
Yeah!
Yeah, just in time!
Return to the past now.
Alone at last, Ulrich!
Just the two of us!
Whoa!
Herb, what the!
Sissi, I love you, too!
You what!?
Cut it out!
Are you out
of your mind or what!
But I got your text message.
“Meet me at the garden shed.
I love you--Sissi.”
We’re gonna give
Tamiya and Milly a real scoop.
Guess who’s gonna make
the front page of the next school paper!
Just keep dreaming, you creep!
In the meantime, you’ve got
some explaining to do
when my father hears about this!
Hey, Sissi! Wait a second!
That’s really such a shame.
We’ve just seen the
beginning and the end
of a beautiful romance!
(LAUGHTER)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO